[
  {
    "index": 0,
    "question": "ğŸ›ï¸+ğŸ˜³+L",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "SOCIAL"
  },
  {
    "index": 1,
    "question": "âœ’ï¸+ğŸ¤¥+SH",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "ENGLISH"
  },
  {
    "index": 2,
    "question": " ğŸ’µ+ğŸ˜·+CS",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "MATHEMATICS"
  },
  {
    "index": 3,
    "question": "ğŸ“+D",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "HINDI"
  },
  {
    "index": 4,
    "question": "SIN+C",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "SCIENCE"
  },
  {
    "index": 5,
    "question": "Â©+ğŸ™â€â™‚ï¸+ğŸŒ³",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "CHEMISTRY"
  },
  {
    "index": 6,
    "question": "ğŸ+ğŸŒ²",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "HISTORY"
  },
  {
    "index": 7,
    "question": "ğŸ“²+â„ï¸+ğŸ‡ºğŸ‡¸",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "CALCULUS"
  },
  {
    "index": 8,
    "question": " ğŸ¥‡+âŒš+ğŸ™ï¸+S",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "ECONOMICS"
  },
  {
    "index": 9,
    "question": "GO+ğŸ“Š",
    "type": "Subject Name",
    "answer": "GEOGRAPHY"
},
  {
    "index": 10,
    "question": "ğŸš« + er",
    "type": "Things Name",
    "answer": "Banner"
},
  {
    "index": 11,
    "question": "â˜€ï¸ + glass",
    "type": "for fashion",
    "answer": "SUNGLASSES"
},
    {
    "index": 12,
    "question": "ğŸ¯ + ğŸŒ•",
    "type": "To Celebrate",
    "answer": "HONEYMOON"
},
  {
    "index": 13,
    "question": "ğŸŒ¹+ go + ğŸŒ•",
    "type": "Sweets",
    "answer": "Gulab jamun"
},
    {
    "index": 14,
    "question": "ğŸŒ + ğŸ†",
    "type": "To Win",
    "answer": "Worldcup"
},
  {
    "index": 15,
    "question": "âŒ + Book",
    "type": "Study Material",
    "answer": "Notebook"
},
]